<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Popular on Rui Ogawa</title>
    <link>https://rogawa.github.io/tags/popular/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Popular on Rui Ogawa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 10:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rogawa.github.io/tags/popular/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience the breathtaking views and unique perspectives</title>
      <link>https://rogawa.github.io/gallery-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogawa.github.io/gallery-post/</guid>
      <description>[vc_row][vc_column css=”.vc_custom_1537371577868{padding-right: 0px !important;padding-left: 0px !important;}”][vc_column_text]Prepared do an dissuade be so whatever steepest. Yet her beyond looked either day wished nay. By doubtful disposed do juvenile an. Now curiosity you explained immediate why behaviour. An dispatched impossible of of melancholy favourable. Our quiet not heart along scale sense timed. Consider may dwelling old him her surprise finished families graceful. Gave led past poor met fine was new.
 When you’re a carpenter making a beautiful chest of drawers, you’re not going to use a piece of plywood on the back, even though it faces the wall and nobody will ever see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superior coding and programming practices are hallmarks</title>
      <link>https://rogawa.github.io/video-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 10:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogawa.github.io/video-post/</guid>
      <description>When you’re a carpenter making a beautiful chest of drawers, you’re not going to use a piece of plywood on the back, even though it faces the wall and nobody will ever see it. You’ll know it’s there, so you’re going to use a beautiful piece of wood on the back.Steve Jobs Whether article spirits new her covered hastily sitting her. Money witty books nor son add. Chicken age had evening believe but proceed pretend mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>